https://www.wiltshire.ac.uk/the-college/policies-procedures

Policies & ProceduresPolicies & Procedures
PoliciesApprenticeship Fees PolicyAdmissions PolicyAttendance and Punctuality PolicyCareers Information, Advice and Guidance PolicyEquality and Diversity PolicyExams PolicyFees PolicyFurther Education Admissions PolicyHealth and Safety PolicyHigher Education Admissions PolicyHigher Education Attendance PolicyHigher Education Fees PolicyLearner Voice PolicySafeguarding PolicySocial Media PolicyStudent Behaviour Management PolicySubcontracting PolicySubmission of Coursework and Assessment PolicyProceduresAcademic Appeals ProcedureAccess Arrangements ProcedureAssessment and Verification ProceduresComments, Compliments and Complaints ProcedureFitness to Study ProcedureMarking and Feedback ProcedurePlagiarism, Malpractice and Maladministration ProcedurePrevent ProcedurePrevent Procedure FlowchartRecognition of Prior Learning ProcedureData ProtectionAcceptable Use PolicyData Protection PolicyPublic Interest and Disclosure (Whistleblowing) PolicyPersonal Data Breach Notification PolicyData Protection Additional Information and GuidanceData Protection StatementFreedom of Information Publication SchemePrivacy NoticeWeb Privacy StatementESFA Student Privacy StatementPrivacy Statement for Visitors and ContractorsAdditional Information and GuidanceEquality and Diversity ReportGender Pay ReportModern Slavery Act StatementPrivacy StatementCollege Strategic Plan
Data ProtectionFind out more
SubcontractingFind out more
Privacy StatementFind out more
Stay Connected
01225 350035
info@wiltshire.ac.uk
VAT Number: 269 7744 41
Website: https://www.wiltshire.ac.uk/Installation ID: 1316316
© 2020 All rights Limited.
